[
    {
        "id": "visitor_agreement",
        "pagename": "visitor agreement",
        "elements": [
            {
                "title": "VISITOR AGREEMENT",
                "date": "LAST UPDATED : Oct 2022",
                "boldparagraph": "<p>Please read this Visitor Agreement carefully. It contains important information regarding your legal rights including mandatory arbitration, no class relief, and waiver of your right to a jury trial. Please take a few minutes to review the section here.</p>",
                "lightparagraph": "<p>This Visitor Agreement applies to the family of informational, educational and entertainment-oriented websites and applications controlled by Indian Media Syndicate, and/or its subsidiary and affiliated entities (collectively, “IMS Group”). Please read this Visitor Agreement; by using the applicable website or application, you accept its terms.</p>",
                "content": "<p>This Visitor Agreement applies to all of the websites and applications where it is posted. Those websites and applications are referred to collectively in this Visitor Agreement as the “IMS TV Sites.” Additional terms and conditions may apply to some services offered on the Discovery Sites. Such terms and conditions may be found at the place where the relevant service is offered. For example, policies governing purchases through IMS.com can be found at the bottom of each IMS.com page. <br /><br />The Web is an evolving medium; we may change the terms of this Visitor Agreement from time to time. By continuing to use any of the IMS Sites after we post any such changes, you accept this Visitor Agreement, as modified. We may change, restrict access to, suspend or discontinue the IMS Sites, or any portion of the IMS Sites, at any time. IMS respects the privacy of our users. Please take a few minutes to review our Privacy Notice.<br /><br /> If you disagree with any material you find on the IMS Sites, we recommend that you respond by noting your disagreement in an appropriate site forum where there is one. We also invite you to bring to our attention any material you believe to be factually inaccurate by contacting our representatives or by contacting Fan Relations at https://corporate-IMS.zendesk.com/hc/en-in. The material that appears on the IMS Sites is for informational and entertainment purposes only. Despite our efforts to provide useful and accurate information, errors may appear from time to time. Before you act on information you’ve found on the IMS Sites, you should confirm any facts that are important to your decision. IMS and its information providers make no warranty as to the reliability, accuracy, timeliness, usefulness or completeness of the information on the IMS Sites. IMS is not responsible for, and cannot guarantee the performance of, goods and services provided by our advertisers or others to whose sites we link. A link to another website does not constitute an endorsement of that site (nor of any product, service or other material offered on that site) by IMS or its licensors. Pursuant to Title 17, Indian Penal Code, Section 512(c)(2), notifications of claimed copyright infringement must be sent to IMS Designated Agent. The Name and Address of Agent Designated to Receive Notification of Claimed Infringement: notices@IMS.com (e-mail). <br /><br />To be effective, the notification must be a written communication that includes the following: <br /><br /><br />A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;<br /><br /> Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site; Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;<br /><br /> Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number and, if available, an e-mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted; A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; and<br /><br /> A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.</p>"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "privacy_notice",
        "pagename": "Privacy Notice",
        "elements": [
            {
                "title": "PRIVACY NOTICE",
                "date": "LAST UPDATED : Oct 2022",
                "boldparagraph": "<p>By accessing and using the Services, you agree to our collection and use of your information in the manner described in this Notice. If you disagree with the terms of this Notice, you should not use the Services.</p>",
                "lightparagraph": "<p>This Notice explains how we collect, use, and share information about users who interact with our websites, applications, our content on connected televisions, or other interactive services that link to or reference this Privacy Notice (“Services”). This Notice does not apply to our collection of information from other features, services, or sources (unless specifically stated), or to third parties that provide information to IMS.</p>",
                "content": "<p>The Services are operated in India and are intended for users located in the India. The Services are therefore governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of India. If you are located outside India, please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the Services will be collected in India and/or transferred to India and will be subject to Indian law. <br/> <br/>By using the Services and/or providing us with information, you (a) consent to the transfer and/or processing of any information to and in India, (b) acknowledge that Indian law may provide a lower standard of protection for information than the laws of your location, (c) understand that we will collect, transfer, store, process and share your information from or about you in accordance with this Notice and Indian law.  <br/> <br/>When you interact with the Services, we collect information that directly identifies you ( i.e., information that would allow someone to identify you or contact you, such as your full name, postal address, e-mail address, or telephone number), as well as information about your use of the Services. Below we describe the different types of information we collect from you and the devices you use when you interact with the Services.  <br/> <br/>Information you provide to us: Some of the Services may permit you to enter contact information and other information about yourself and others. We collect and store any information you enter through the Services. For example, you may provide: <br/> <br/> your name, postal address, e-mail address, phone number, profile picture, birthday, or other information, such as when you register with our Services, create or edit your user profile, sign up to receive newsletters, or enter in a contest or sweepstakes;  <br/>certain demographic information, such as your age, gender, or income bracket, when you participate in a survey or poll;  <br/>information in postings, comments, or forums (such as chat rooms, message boards, or similar public forums) within the Services, and in non-public messages you send to other users of the Services; <br/> nutrition and dietary preference information when you search for recipes within the Services;  <br/>your first and last name, your address, and your credit card and billing information if you purchase of a product at the IMS Store or subscribe to one of IMS's paid Services; or <br/> your e-mail address, communications, and files when you send to us a message by e-mail, through our Customer Support portal, or through other communication services. <br/> Information we collect automatically from your devices: When you interact with the Services, certain information about your use of the Services is automatically collected. This information includes information about the devices used to access the Services, such as Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, your device ID and other unique device identifiers, mobile network information, information about how the device is interacting with our Services, hardware model, and the type and version of your device’s operating system or web browser. We also collect information about how you use our Services, such as pages viewed and the order of such pages, content (including video content) or advertising you view within the Services; the length of time you interact with the Services; search queries entered within the Services; error logs; websites and other services you visit before and after visiting an IMS site; and other similar information. Much of this information is collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies. Please see our Tracking Technologies Notice for further information, including your choices in relation to the use of these technologies.</p>"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "website_accessibility_statement",
        "pagename": "Website accessibility statement",
        "elements": [
            {
                "title": "WEBSITE ACCESSIBILITY STATEMENT",
                "date": "LAST UPDATED : Oct 2022",
                "boldparagraph": "<p>This website is one of the family of informational, educational and entertainment-oriented applications and websites brought to you by Indian Media Syndicate and its subsidiaries and affiliates (“IMS”).</p>",
                "lightparagraph": "<p>IMS is committed to facilitating and improving the accessibility and usability of its websites and applications. IMS strives to ensure that its websites, applications, and content are accessible to persons with disabilities, including users of screen reader technology. We endeavor to maintain our websites in-line with the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines, which also brings the websites into conformance with the Indians with Disabilities Act of 2006.</p>",
                "content": "<p><h4>Disclaimer</h4> Our efforts to maintain accessibility and usability are ongoing. While we strive to make our websites as accessible as possible, some issues may be encountered by different assistive technology.<br/><br/> <h4>Audio Descriptions</h4> Scheduling information for IMS content containing audio descriptions airing on our linear networks is available here <br/><br/><h4>Contact Us</h4> If at any time you have specific questions or concerns about the accessibility of any particular web page on this website, please contact our Fan Relations department. If you do encounter an accessibility issue, please be sure to specify the web page and nature of the issue in your message, and we will make all reasonable efforts to make that page or the information contained therein accessible for you.</p>"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "code_of_ethics",
        "pagename": "code of ethics",
        "elements": [
            {
                "title": "CODE OF <br/>ETHICS",
                "date": "LAST UPDATED : Oct 2022",
                "boldparagraph": "<p>Indian Media Syndicate strives to be the global leader in real life entertainment, serving passionate explorers around the world with scientific journalism that inspires, informs and entertains.</p>",
                "lightparagraph": "<p>Integrity matters.<br/> When we conduct business ethically, we send a message to our consumers, business partners, shareholders and other stakeholders that they can put their trust in us. By doing the right thing, we not only protect our reputation, but also help Indian Media Syndicate (“IMS”) to thrive.<br/> To that end, we have created this Code of Ethics (“Code”). It provides standards for: ensuring compliance with applicable laws, regulations and company policies; promoting integrity and the highest standards of ethical conduct; and helping us to avoid even the appearance of anything improper in our business activities.</p>",
                "content": "<p><h4>WHO MUST FOLLOW THIS CODE</h4> This Code applies to all directors, officers, executives and employees of IMS and its subsidiaries around the world, including joint ventures that are subject to it. It applies everywhere we do business and any time anybody represents IMS. <br> <br> We all play a role in ensuring that IMS conducts business ethically every day and all over the world. As an employee, you have a responsibility to: <br> • Act with integrity, especially when making difficult choices; <br> • Be familiar with the information contained in this Code as well as in company policies and applicable laws, paying particular attention to the requirements that relate to your job and work location; <br> • Complete required employee training in a timely manner and keep up-to-date on current standards and expectations; <br> • Seek guidance whenever you encounter a situation where how to “do the right thing” is unclear; <br> • Promptly report concerns about conduct that may be inconsistent with our Guiding Principles, this Code, our policies or the law—do not undertake an investigation on your own; and <br> • Cooperate and tell the truth when participating in an investigation, audit or other inquiry. <br> <br> Violations of this Code, the company’s policies and/or applicable laws may subject employees to disciplinary action that could, in the most serious circumstances, include responsibility for financial damages and/or termination of employment; employees may also face criminal prosecution. <br> <br> Business partners—including vendors, suppliers, consultants, sales representatives and temporary employees—serve as an extension of IMS and therefore are also expected to comply with this Code. We will take appropriate measures where we believe our business partners have not met our expectations or their contractual obligations. In particular, if any provision of this Code conflicts with a local law or requirement, you should seek guidance from your Human Resources manager or Legal | Ethics & Compliance</p>"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "faqs",
        "pagename": "frequently asked questions",
        "elements": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "Nulla neque libero, convallis eget, eleifend luctus, ultricies eu, nibh.",
                "answer": "eget eros elementum pellentesque quisque porta volutpat erat quisque erat eros viverra eget congue eget semper",
                "time": "2022-04-20T18:17:19Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "Vestibulum rutrum rutrum neque.",
                "answer": "pellentesque eget nunc donec quis orci eget orci vehicula condimentum curabitur in libero ut massa",
                "time": "2021-08-12T14:00:30Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "Maecenas ut massa quis augue luctus tincidunt.",
                "answer": "in quis justo maecenas rhoncus aliquam lacus morbi quis tortor id nulla ultrices aliquet",
                "time": "2021-12-12T02:22:56Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "In blandit ultrices enim.",
                "answer": "porta volutpat quam pede lobortis ligula sit amet eleifend pede libero quis orci nullam molestie nibh in lectus pellentesque",
                "time": "2021-10-01T14:00:47Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "Mauris lacinia sapien quis libero.",
                "answer": "nunc commodo placerat praesent blandit nam nulla integer pede justo lacinia",
                "time": "2021-07-31T06:37:35Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "Duis aliquam convallis nunc.",
                "answer": "pretium iaculis diam erat fermentum justo nec condimentum neque sapien placerat ante nulla justo aliquam quis turpis",
                "time": "2021-08-14T11:47:30Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "Fusce posuere felis sed lacus.",
                "answer": "pede justo lacinia eget tincidunt eget tempus vel pede morbi porttitor",
                "time": "2022-05-07T15:51:43Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "Nulla tempus.",
                "answer": "aliquet massa id lobortis convallis tortor risus dapibus augue vel accumsan tellus",
                "time": "2021-08-06T09:00:39Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "Suspendisse accumsan tortor quis turpis.",
                "answer": "libero convallis eget eleifend luctus ultricies eu nibh quisque id justo sit amet sapien dignissim vestibulum vestibulum ante ipsum primis",
                "time": "2022-04-16T02:41:32Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "Nullam orci pede, venenatis non, sodales sed, tincidunt eu, felis.",
                "answer": "potenti nullam porttitor lacus at turpis donec posuere metus vitae",
                "time": "2021-08-09T12:55:37Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "In hac habitasse platea dictumst.",
                "answer": "in sapien iaculis congue vivamus metus arcu adipiscing molestie hendrerit at vulputate vitae nisl aenean lectus pellentesque",
                "time": "2022-02-21T15:42:29Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "Curabitur convallis.",
                "answer": "nisi at nibh in hac habitasse platea dictumst aliquam augue",
                "time": "2021-11-22T05:19:14Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "Morbi a ipsum.",
                "answer": "ut massa volutpat convallis morbi odio odio elementum eu interdum eu tincidunt in leo maecenas",
                "time": "2022-03-23T04:54:10Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "Etiam justo.",
                "answer": "faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia curae nulla dapibus dolor vel est donec odio justo sollicitudin ut suscipit a",
                "time": "2021-11-25T14:04:22Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "Aenean auctor gravida sem.",
                "answer": "varius nulla facilisi cras non velit nec nisi vulputate nonummy maecenas tincidunt lacus at velit vivamus vel nulla eget eros",
                "time": "2021-06-14T21:56:08Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "Integer non velit.",
                "answer": "placerat praesent blandit nam nulla integer pede justo lacinia eget tincidunt eget tempus vel pede morbi porttitor lorem id",
                "time": "2021-11-19T12:36:21Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia Curae; Mauris viverra diam vitae quam.",
                "answer": "sapien quis libero nullam sit amet turpis elementum ligula vehicula consequat",
                "time": "2022-01-02T04:45:34Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.",
                "answer": "a suscipit nulla elit ac nulla sed vel enim sit amet nunc viverra dapibus nulla suscipit ligula",
                "time": "2022-04-29T08:16:56Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "Morbi vel lectus in quam fringilla rhoncus.",
                "answer": "elementum nullam varius nulla facilisi cras non velit nec nisi vulputate nonummy",
                "time": "2022-03-03T13:48:21Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "Morbi a ipsum.",
                "answer": "pede lobortis ligula sit amet eleifend pede libero quis orci nullam molestie nibh in",
                "time": "2021-06-03T19:36:33Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "Vivamus vestibulum sagittis sapien.",
                "answer": "id lobortis convallis tortor risus dapibus augue vel accumsan tellus nisi eu orci mauris lacinia sapien quis libero nullam",
                "time": "2021-12-18T18:45:10Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "Quisque id justo sit amet sapien dignissim vestibulum.",
                "answer": "dui vel nisl duis ac nibh fusce lacus purus aliquet",
                "time": "2022-05-27T10:31:36Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "Fusce consequat.",
                "answer": "pellentesque ultrices phasellus id sapien in sapien iaculis congue vivamus metus arcu adipiscing molestie hendrerit",
                "time": "2021-12-28T07:06:56Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "Proin leo odio, porttitor id, consequat in, consequat ut, nulla.",
                "answer": "sed vestibulum sit amet cursus id turpis integer aliquet massa id lobortis convallis tortor risus dapibus",
                "time": "2022-01-15T11:25:12Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "Quisque arcu libero, rutrum ac, lobortis vel, dapibus at, diam.",
                "answer": "mattis egestas metus aenean fermentum donec ut mauris eget massa tempor convallis nulla neque libero convallis eget eleifend luctus ultricies",
                "time": "2021-11-07T19:22:22Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "Nam congue, risus semper porta volutpat, quam pede lobortis ligula, sit amet eleifend pede libero quis orci.",
                "answer": "tellus nulla ut erat id mauris vulputate elementum nullam varius nulla facilisi cras non velit nec nisi",
                "time": "2021-07-12T11:19:19Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "Morbi odio odio, elementum eu, interdum eu, tincidunt in, leo.",
                "answer": "consequat ut nulla sed accumsan felis ut at dolor quis odio consequat",
                "time": "2021-07-13T04:42:16Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "Integer a nibh.",
                "answer": "ultrices libero non mattis pulvinar nulla pede ullamcorper augue a suscipit nulla elit ac",
                "time": "2022-05-05T12:31:03Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "Suspendisse accumsan tortor quis turpis.",
                "answer": "sapien urna pretium nisl ut volutpat sapien arcu sed augue aliquam erat volutpat in congue",
                "time": "2022-03-19T07:15:49Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "Nulla tellus.",
                "answer": "sagittis sapien cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes",
                "time": "2022-05-02T14:17:31Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "Curabitur convallis.",
                "answer": "leo maecenas pulvinar lobortis est phasellus sit amet erat nulla tempus vivamus in felis",
                "time": "2021-08-01T07:20:14Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "Nunc rhoncus dui vel sem.",
                "answer": "neque libero convallis eget eleifend luctus ultricies eu nibh quisque id justo",
                "time": "2022-05-13T06:08:30Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "Vivamus metus arcu, adipiscing molestie, hendrerit at, vulputate vitae, nisl.",
                "answer": "pellentesque ultrices phasellus id sapien in sapien iaculis congue vivamus metus arcu adipiscing molestie hendrerit",
                "time": "2021-10-27T01:07:11Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "Suspendisse accumsan tortor quis turpis.",
                "answer": "non mi integer ac neque duis bibendum morbi non quam nec dui luctus rutrum",
                "time": "2021-06-27T17:12:49Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit.",
                "answer": "nulla suspendisse potenti cras in purus eu magna vulputate luctus cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes nascetur",
                "time": "2021-08-31T11:42:00Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "Cras mi pede, malesuada in, imperdiet et, commodo vulputate, justo.",
                "answer": "accumsan odio curabitur convallis duis consequat dui nec nisi volutpat eleifend donec ut",
                "time": "2021-08-21T12:10:55Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "Maecenas tincidunt lacus at velit.",
                "answer": "platea dictumst etiam faucibus cursus urna ut tellus nulla ut erat id",
                "time": "2021-06-24T04:08:25Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "Vestibulum quam sapien, varius ut, blandit non, interdum in, ante.",
                "answer": "pulvinar lobortis est phasellus sit amet erat nulla tempus vivamus in felis eu sapien cursus vestibulum proin eu mi nulla",
                "time": "2021-08-09T06:07:04Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "Nunc rhoncus dui vel sem.",
                "answer": "nisi eu orci mauris lacinia sapien quis libero nullam sit amet turpis",
                "time": "2022-03-16T02:29:11Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "Nullam varius.",
                "answer": "aliquet massa id lobortis convallis tortor risus dapibus augue vel",
                "time": "2022-05-02T18:07:25Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "Cras mi pede, malesuada in, imperdiet et, commodo vulputate, justo.",
                "answer": "congue diam id ornare imperdiet sapien urna pretium nisl ut volutpat",
                "time": "2022-03-30T06:06:29Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "Donec diam neque, vestibulum eget, vulputate ut, ultrices vel, augue.",
                "answer": "vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices",
                "time": "2022-02-14T13:14:52Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "In blandit ultrices enim.",
                "answer": "vel augue vestibulum rutrum rutrum neque aenean auctor gravida sem",
                "time": "2021-09-23T17:41:13Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "Vestibulum ac est lacinia nisi venenatis tristique.",
                "answer": "pellentesque volutpat dui maecenas tristique est et tempus semper est quam pharetra magna ac consequat metus",
                "time": "2022-04-13T22:38:18Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "Duis aliquam convallis nunc.",
                "answer": "egestas metus aenean fermentum donec ut mauris eget massa tempor convallis nulla neque libero convallis eget",
                "time": "2021-10-07T09:40:13Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "Cras pellentesque volutpat dui.",
                "answer": "sed sagittis nam congue risus semper porta volutpat quam pede lobortis",
                "time": "2022-05-13T23:27:50Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "Nullam porttitor lacus at turpis.",
                "answer": "pellentesque ultrices mattis odio donec vitae nisi nam ultrices libero non",
                "time": "2021-08-27T23:25:09Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "Nullam porttitor lacus at turpis.",
                "answer": "vivamus tortor duis mattis egestas metus aenean fermentum donec ut mauris eget massa tempor convallis nulla neque libero convallis eget",
                "time": "2022-01-26T10:47:38Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit.",
                "answer": "eget massa tempor convallis nulla neque libero convallis eget eleifend luctus ultricies eu nibh",
                "time": "2021-08-28T03:12:31Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "Donec odio justo, sollicitudin ut, suscipit a, feugiat et, eros.",
                "answer": "libero rutrum ac lobortis vel dapibus at diam nam tristique tortor eu pede",
                "time": "2021-08-11T09:55:47Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "Integer ac neque.",
                "answer": "a libero nam dui proin leo odio porttitor id consequat in consequat ut nulla sed",
                "time": "2021-08-22T05:15:22Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "Sed vel enim sit amet nunc viverra dapibus.",
                "answer": "quisque porta volutpat erat quisque erat eros viverra eget congue eget semper rutrum nulla nunc",
                "time": "2021-07-29T00:39:35Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "Maecenas rhoncus aliquam lacus.",
                "answer": "fringilla rhoncus mauris enim leo rhoncus sed vestibulum sit amet cursus id turpis integer aliquet massa id lobortis convallis",
                "time": "2021-12-14T16:51:03Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia Curae; Duis faucibus accumsan odio.",
                "answer": "est lacinia nisi venenatis tristique fusce congue diam id ornare imperdiet sapien urna pretium nisl ut volutpat",
                "time": "2022-04-04T06:00:53Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "Curabitur in libero ut massa volutpat convallis.",
                "answer": "tortor duis mattis egestas metus aenean fermentum donec ut mauris eget massa",
                "time": "2021-11-06T13:23:03Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "Morbi non quam nec dui luctus rutrum.",
                "answer": "lacus curabitur at ipsum ac tellus semper interdum mauris ullamcorper purus",
                "time": "2022-01-21T16:57:19Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "Praesent id massa id nisl venenatis lacinia.",
                "answer": "ultrices posuere cubilia curae donec pharetra magna vestibulum aliquet ultrices erat tortor sollicitudin mi sit amet lobortis",
                "time": "2022-01-07T18:37:15Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "Proin at turpis a pede posuere nonummy.",
                "answer": "duis bibendum morbi non quam nec dui luctus rutrum nulla tellus in sagittis dui vel nisl",
                "time": "2022-04-19T01:48:24Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "Proin interdum mauris non ligula pellentesque ultrices.",
                "answer": "sem sed sagittis nam congue risus semper porta volutpat quam pede lobortis ligula",
                "time": "2021-11-20T10:19:05Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "Vivamus metus arcu, adipiscing molestie, hendrerit at, vulputate vitae, nisl.",
                "answer": "ut erat id mauris vulputate elementum nullam varius nulla facilisi cras non velit nec nisi vulputate nonummy",
                "time": "2021-12-09T07:19:01Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "Nunc nisl.",
                "answer": "nibh ligula nec sem duis aliquam convallis nunc proin at turpis a pede posuere",
                "time": "2021-07-30T01:56:30Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "Mauris sit amet eros.",
                "answer": "elit proin interdum mauris non ligula pellentesque ultrices phasellus id sapien in sapien iaculis",
                "time": "2022-02-14T20:23:55Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "Nullam molestie nibh in lectus.",
                "answer": "ligula vehicula consequat morbi a ipsum integer a nibh in quis justo maecenas rhoncus aliquam",
                "time": "2022-04-21T15:28:12Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "In blandit ultrices enim.",
                "answer": "congue vivamus metus arcu adipiscing molestie hendrerit at vulputate vitae",
                "time": "2021-10-05T13:09:24Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "Aliquam augue quam, sollicitudin vitae, consectetuer eget, rutrum at, lorem.",
                "answer": "pede justo lacinia eget tincidunt eget tempus vel pede morbi porttitor lorem id ligula suspendisse ornare consequat lectus in",
                "time": "2021-11-24T03:53:13Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "Aenean fermentum.",
                "answer": "duis bibendum felis sed interdum venenatis turpis enim blandit mi in porttitor pede justo eu massa donec dapibus",
                "time": "2022-03-15T12:28:31Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "Integer ac leo.",
                "answer": "gravida nisi at nibh in hac habitasse platea dictumst aliquam augue quam sollicitudin vitae consectetuer eget",
                "time": "2021-12-28T08:35:51Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.",
                "answer": "justo lacinia eget tincidunt eget tempus vel pede morbi porttitor lorem id ligula suspendisse ornare consequat lectus",
                "time": "2022-05-09T09:27:22Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia Curae; Duis faucibus accumsan odio.",
                "answer": "tincidunt nulla mollis molestie lorem quisque ut erat curabitur gravida nisi at nibh in",
                "time": "2022-05-17T09:39:00Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "Donec posuere metus vitae ipsum.",
                "answer": "enim leo rhoncus sed vestibulum sit amet cursus id turpis integer aliquet massa id",
                "time": "2022-05-15T04:27:41Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "Proin leo odio, porttitor id, consequat in, consequat ut, nulla.",
                "answer": "sit amet cursus id turpis integer aliquet massa id lobortis",
                "time": "2022-03-11T06:23:46Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "Maecenas ut massa quis augue luctus tincidunt.",
                "answer": "pretium quis lectus suspendisse potenti in eleifend quam a odio in hac habitasse platea dictumst",
                "time": "2022-01-11T01:03:14Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "Nulla neque libero, convallis eget, eleifend luctus, ultricies eu, nibh.",
                "answer": "venenatis non sodales sed tincidunt eu felis fusce posuere felis sed lacus morbi",
                "time": "2021-09-26T04:18:21Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "Nullam porttitor lacus at turpis.",
                "answer": "nisl ut volutpat sapien arcu sed augue aliquam erat volutpat in congue etiam justo",
                "time": "2022-01-18T10:48:53Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "Quisque id justo sit amet sapien dignissim vestibulum.",
                "answer": "quam sollicitudin vitae consectetuer eget rutrum at lorem integer tincidunt ante vel ipsum",
                "time": "2021-11-16T20:54:25Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "Mauris lacinia sapien quis libero.",
                "answer": "vestibulum rutrum rutrum neque aenean auctor gravida sem praesent id massa id nisl venenatis lacinia aenean sit",
                "time": "2022-04-21T07:49:12Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "Praesent id massa id nisl venenatis lacinia.",
                "answer": "pulvinar sed nisl nunc rhoncus dui vel sem sed sagittis nam congue risus semper porta volutpat quam pede lobortis ligula",
                "time": "2021-06-23T05:05:41Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "Maecenas tristique, est et tempus semper, est quam pharetra magna, ac consequat metus sapien ut nunc.",
                "answer": "lacus purus aliquet at feugiat non pretium quis lectus suspendisse potenti in eleifend quam",
                "time": "2021-11-27T12:17:28Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "Donec quis orci eget orci vehicula condimentum.",
                "answer": "proin interdum mauris non ligula pellentesque ultrices phasellus id sapien",
                "time": "2021-07-07T00:31:30Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "Proin risus.",
                "answer": "ut nulla sed accumsan felis ut at dolor quis odio consequat",
                "time": "2021-08-03T17:12:27Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "Morbi quis tortor id nulla ultrices aliquet.",
                "answer": "semper interdum mauris ullamcorper purus sit amet nulla quisque arcu libero",
                "time": "2021-12-13T20:41:16Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "Nulla facilisi.",
                "answer": "lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetuer adipiscing elit proin risus praesent lectus vestibulum",
                "time": "2021-09-21T16:24:54Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "In hac habitasse platea dictumst.",
                "answer": "id ligula suspendisse ornare consequat lectus in est risus auctor sed tristique in tempus sit amet",
                "time": "2022-05-11T12:00:53Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "Maecenas tristique, est et tempus semper, est quam pharetra magna, ac consequat metus sapien ut nunc.",
                "answer": "vitae consectetuer eget rutrum at lorem integer tincidunt ante vel ipsum praesent blandit",
                "time": "2022-03-31T21:49:49Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "Etiam vel augue.",
                "answer": "morbi non lectus aliquam sit amet diam in magna bibendum imperdiet nullam orci pede",
                "time": "2021-09-20T07:20:02Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "Pellentesque viverra pede ac diam.",
                "answer": "vulputate luctus cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes nascetur ridiculus mus vivamus vestibulum sagittis sapien",
                "time": "2022-02-28T06:01:30Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "Maecenas pulvinar lobortis est.",
                "answer": "tortor id nulla ultrices aliquet maecenas leo odio condimentum id luctus nec molestie sed justo pellentesque viverra pede ac diam",
                "time": "2021-11-26T20:38:01Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "Proin risus.",
                "answer": "erat nulla tempus vivamus in felis eu sapien cursus vestibulum proin eu mi nulla ac enim in tempor turpis nec",
                "time": "2022-02-08T13:36:07Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "In sagittis dui vel nisl.",
                "answer": "nisl nunc nisl duis bibendum felis sed interdum venenatis turpis enim blandit mi in porttitor pede justo eu",
                "time": "2021-09-15T16:43:05Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "Aenean auctor gravida sem.",
                "answer": "purus sit amet nulla quisque arcu libero rutrum ac lobortis vel dapibus at diam nam tristique tortor eu",
                "time": "2022-01-03T19:29:43Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "Vestibulum quam sapien, varius ut, blandit non, interdum in, ante.",
                "answer": "blandit nam nulla integer pede justo lacinia eget tincidunt eget tempus vel pede morbi porttitor lorem id ligula suspendisse",
                "time": "2021-08-03T15:04:00Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "In blandit ultrices enim.",
                "answer": "proin at turpis a pede posuere nonummy integer non velit donec diam neque vestibulum eget vulputate ut ultrices vel",
                "time": "2022-01-12T22:34:59Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "Morbi sem mauris, laoreet ut, rhoncus aliquet, pulvinar sed, nisl.",
                "answer": "est risus auctor sed tristique in tempus sit amet sem fusce consequat",
                "time": "2022-03-28T00:11:30Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "Sed ante.",
                "answer": "quam pharetra magna ac consequat metus sapien ut nunc vestibulum ante ipsum primis in",
                "time": "2022-05-01T09:22:19Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "Phasellus id sapien in sapien iaculis congue.",
                "answer": "erat quisque erat eros viverra eget congue eget semper rutrum nulla nunc",
                "time": "2021-07-08T23:11:40Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "Proin eu mi.",
                "answer": "sed tristique in tempus sit amet sem fusce consequat nulla nisl nunc nisl duis bibendum felis sed interdum venenatis turpis",
                "time": "2021-10-01T09:50:02Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia Curae; Mauris viverra diam vitae quam.",
                "answer": "pede lobortis ligula sit amet eleifend pede libero quis orci nullam molestie nibh in",
                "time": "2021-08-04T01:47:04Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "Vestibulum rutrum rutrum neque.",
                "answer": "dictumst maecenas ut massa quis augue luctus tincidunt nulla mollis molestie",
                "time": "2022-01-08T13:29:56Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "Etiam pretium iaculis justo.",
                "answer": "quam suspendisse potenti nullam porttitor lacus at turpis donec posuere metus vitae ipsum aliquam",
                "time": "2022-01-13T09:41:23Z"
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "Aliquam non mauris.",
                "answer": "maecenas pulvinar lobortis est phasellus sit amet erat nulla tempus vivamus",
                "time": "2021-08-16T03:11:30Z"
            }
        ]
    }
]